A Guide to the Institute of International Education records, Alumni and Historical Files, RG 1 FA1289
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Historical Files, 3
  - British Summer Schools Publicity- Correspondence with All Universities - Student Reports 1959 (Reel 32, Side 1, Index 3), Reel 32, Side 1, Index 3 (Reel 32)
  - British Summer Schools Oxford University Correspondence 1959 (Reel 32, Side 2, Index 27), Reel 32, Side 2, Index 27 (Reel 32)
  - British Summer Schools Selection Committee - Correspondence with United States Universities - Private Scholarships (1955-1956) - Council on Student Travel - Cunard 1959 (Reel 32, Side 1, Index 4), Reel 32, Side 1, Index 4 (Reel 32)
  - British Summer Schools Memos - Form Letters - Miscellaneous Correspondence - Mailing Lists - English Speaking Union - Weekly Status Reports 1959 (Reel 32, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 32, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 32)
  - British Summer Schools Mr. Frank Jessup's Trip to the United States 1959 (Reel 32, Side 2, Index 26), Reel 32, Side 2, Index 26 (Reel 32)
  - Colleges 1932 (Reel 4, Side 1, Index 11), Reel 4, Side 1, Index 11 (Reel 4)
  - Canada - Special Projects Canada Plan B 1936 (Reel 8, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 8, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 8)
  - Canada - Special Projects Canada Plan B 1937 (Reel 8, Side 2, Index 29), Reel 8, Side 2, Index 29 (Reel 8)
  - Canada Correspondence RE Fellowship For 1942-1942 and 1942-1943 (Reel 12, Side 1, Index 32), Reel 12, Side 1, Index 32 (Reel 12)
  - Canada 1942 (Reel 12, Side 2, Index 22), Reel 12, Side 2, Index 22 (Reel 12)
  - Canada 1943 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 52), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 52 (Reel 13)
  - Canada 1944 (Reel 13, Side 2, Index 21), Reel 13, Side 2, Index 21 (Reel 13)
  - Canada 1946 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 15), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 15 (Reel 15)
  - Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation Traveling Fund 1928 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 3), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 3 (Reel 3)
  - Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation Oberlander Trust 1931 (Reel 11, Side 2, Index 13), Reel 11, Side 2, Index 13 (Reel 11)
  - Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation 1931 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 3)
  - Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation 1933 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 2), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 2 (Reel 11)
  - Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation 1935 (Reel 5, Side 1, Index 12), Reel 5, Side 1, Index 12 (Reel 5)
  - Steven Duggan Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation Re Correspondence of Dr. Judah L. Magnes with Dr. Wilbur K. Thomas about Germany 1935 (Reel 17, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 17, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 17)
  - Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation 1937 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 7)
  - Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation 1942 (Reel 12, Side 2, Index 28), Reel 12, Side 2, Index 28 (Reel 12)
  - Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation 1943 (Reel 14, Side 1, Index 3), Reel 14, Side 1, Index 3 (Reel 14)
  - Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation 1944 (Reel 14, Side 1, Index 23), Reel 14, Side 1, Index 23 (Reel 14)
  - Steven Duggan Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation 1945 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 25), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 25 (Reel 15)
  - Steven Duggan Carl Schurz Memorial 1947 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 38), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 38 (Reel 15)
  - Carnegie Corporation 1932 (Reel 4, Side 1, Index 7), Reel 4, Side 1, Index 7 (Reel 4)
  - Carnegie Corporation 1933 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 3), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 3 (Reel 11)
  - Carnegie Corporation, Edowment, Foundation 1942 (Reel 12, Side 2, Index 29), Reel 12, Side 2, Index 29 (Reel 12)
  - Carnegie Corporation and Endowment 1943 (Reel 13, Side 2, Index 39), Reel 13, Side 2, Index 39 (Reel 13)
  - Carnegie Corporation 1945 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 26), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 26 (Reel 15)
  - Carnegie Corporation 1946 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 8), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 8 (Reel 16)
  - China Willard Straight Fellowship 1928-29 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 2), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 2 (Reel 3)
  - China Willard Straight Fellowship 1930 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 9), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 9 (Reel 3)
  - China Willard Straight Fellowship 1931 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 13), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 13 (Reel 3)
  - China Willard Straight Fellowship 1932 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 26), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 26 (Reel 3)
  - Special Projects China 1932 (Reel 8, Side 1, Index 18), Reel 8, Side 1, Index 18 (Reel 8)
  - China 1933 (Reel 4, Side 1, Index 2), Reel 4, Side 1, Index 2 (Reel 4)
  - China 1940 (Reel 10, Side 1, Index 17), Reel 10, Side 1, Index 17 (Reel 10)
  - China Special Projects DR.CS.LO, DR. FU Shang-Ling 1940 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 25), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 25 (Reel 2)
  - Stephen Duggan China Institute in America 1942 (Reel 12, Side 2, Index 30), Reel 12, Side 2, Index 30 (Reel 12)
  - China Institute in America 1943 (Reel 13, Side 2, Index 37), Reel 13, Side 2, Index 37 (Reel 13)
  - China General 1943 (Reel 13, Side 2, Index 36), Reel 13, Side 2, Index 36 (Reel 13)
  - China 1943 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 6), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 6 (Reel 13)
  - China General 1944 (Reel 13, Side 2, Index 20), Reel 13, Side 2, Index 20 (Reel 13)
  - China 1944 (Reel 13, Side 2, Index 16), Reel 13, Side 2, Index 16 (Reel 13)
  - Stephen Duggan China Institute in America 1944 (Reel 14, Side 1, Index 15), Reel 14, Side 1, Index 15 (Reel 14)
  - Stephen Duggan China Institute in America 1945 (Reel 14, Side 2, Index 13), Reel 14, Side 2, Index 13 (Reel 14)
  - China 1946 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 14), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 14 (Reel 15)
  - Stephen Duggan China Institute in America 1946 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 16)
  - China United Service to China, Inc. 1946-47 (Reel 16, Side 2, Index 9), Reel 16, Side 2, Index 9 (Reel 16)
  - Stephen Duggan China Institute in America 1947 (Reel 15, Side 2, Index 6), Reel 15, Side 2, Index 6 (Reel 15)
  - Conferences in the U.S. 1937 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 36), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 36 (Reel 7)
  - Conferences in other countries 1937 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 37), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 37 (Reel 7)
  - Conferences in New York 1937 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 7)
  - Conferences in other countries 1937-38 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 46), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 46 (Reel 7)
  - Conferences in New York 1942 (Reel 12, Side 2, Index 26), Reel 12, Side 2, Index 26 (Reel 12)
  - Conferences in the United States 1942 (Reel 12, Side 2, Index 27), Reel 12, Side 2, Index 27 (Reel 12)
  - General Conference of Foreign Student Advisors - Cleveland, April 28, 1942 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 28), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 28 (Reel 16)
  - General Conference of Foreign Student Advisors - Cleveland, April 29, 1942 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 29), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 29 (Reel 16)
  - General Conference of Foreign Student Advisors - Cleveland, April 29, 1942 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 30), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 30 (Reel 16)
  - General Conference of Foreign Student Advisors - Cleveland, April 30, 1942 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 31), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 31 (Reel 16)
  - National Peace Conference 1942 (Reel 12, Side 2, Index 34), Reel 12, Side 2, Index 34 (Reel 12)
  - National Peace Conference 1943 (Reel 14, Side 1, Index 2), Reel 14, Side 1, Index 2 (Reel 14)
  - U.S. Student Assembly 1943 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 13)
  - General Conferences in New York 1946 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 12), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 12 (Reel 16)
  - General Conferences in the U.S. 1946 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 3), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 3 (Reel 16)
  - General Conferences in in other Countries 1946 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 11), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 11 (Reel 16)
  - Conference of College and University Administrators and Foreign Student Advisors 1946 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 4), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 4 (Reel 16)
  - General - 11E Report Conference on Foreign Student Problems and Policies 1946 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 41), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 41 (Reel 15)
  - National Peace Conference 1946 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 2), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 2 (Reel 16)
  - General 11E Report Conference of Foreign Student Advisors - Chicago 1947 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 37), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 37 (Reel 15)
  - General 11E Orientation Conference for Scholarship Students September 1947 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 32), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 32 (Reel 16)
  - General Conference - September 1947, Dean Carman's Speech 1947 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 13), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 13 (Reel 16)
  - Conferences in the U.S. 1947 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 40), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 40 (Reel 15)
  - General Re Conferences in other Countries 1947 (Reel 15, Side 2, Index 7), Reel 15, Side 2, Index 7 (Reel 15)
  - Information - General List of International Conferences and Meetings July 1948-December 1949-1948 (Reel 28, Side 2, Index 19), Reel 28, Side 2, Index 19 (Reel 28)
  - American Council on Education Conference on the Role of Colleges and Universities in International Understadning - Donald J. Shank - Estes Park, Colorado 1949 (Reel 17, Side 1, Index 35), Reel 17, Side 1, Index 35 (Reel 17)
  - General Conferences in U.S. 1949-50 (Reel 19, Side 2, Index 10), Reel 19, Side 2, Index 10 (Reel 19)
  - National Assn. of Foreign Student Advisers (NAFSA) - Committee on Training and Trainees 1949, 1950 Conferences (Reel 19, Side 2, Index 16), Reel 19, Side 2, Index 16 (Reel 19)
  - General Lincoln University Conference on African Affairs and Inauguration of Institute of African Studies, Nov. 17-18 1959 (Reel 19, Side 2, Index 7), Reel 19, Side 2, Index 7 (Reel 19)
  - Council on Foreign Relations 1931 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 16), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 16 (Reel 3)
  - Council on Foreign Relations 1932 (Reel 4, Side 1, Index 18), Reel 4, Side 1, Index 18 (Reel 4)
  - Stephen Duggan - Council on Foreign Relations 1933 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 4), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 4 (Reel 11)
  - Council on Foreign Relations 1935 (Reel 5, Side 1, Index 13), Reel 5, Side 1, Index 13 (Reel 5)
  - Stephen Duggan - Council on Foreign Relations 1942 (Reel 12, Side 2, Index 31), Reel 12, Side 2, Index 31 (Reel 12)
  - Stephen Duggan - Council on Foreign Relations 1943 (Reel 13, Side 2, Index 38), Reel 13, Side 2, Index 38 (Reel 13)
  - Stephen Duggan - Council on Foreign Relations 1944 (Reel 14, Side 1, Index 24), Reel 14, Side 1, Index 24 (Reel 14)
  - Stephen Duggan - Council on Foreign Relations 1945 (Reel 14, Side 2, Index 12), Reel 14, Side 2, Index 12 (Reel 14)
  - Stephen Duggan - Council on Foreign Relations 1946 (Reel 15, Side 2, Index 27), Reel 15, Side 2, Index 27 (Reel 15)
  - Council on Student Travel - John S. Hollister - General A-Z 1951 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 25)
  - Council on Student Travel - John S. Hollister - Reports 1951 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 6), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 6 (Reel 25)
  - Council on Student Travel - John S. Hollister - General A-Z 1952 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 7), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 7 (Reel 25)
  - Council on Student Travel - John S. Hollister - General A-Z 1953 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 8), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 8 (Reel 25)
  - Council on Student Travel - John E. Bowman - General A-Z 1954 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 25)
  - Council on Student Travel - John E. Bowman - General A-Z January-May 1955 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 10), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 10 (Reel 25)
  - Council on Student Travel - John E. Bowman - General A-Z June-December 1955 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 11), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 11 (Reel 25)
  - Country Files - China, Czechoslovakia, England - General Correspondance 1919-25 (Reel 2, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 2, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 2)
  - Country Files General Africa, Czechoslovakia 1928 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 2), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 2 (Reel 18)
  - Country Files Special Projects - Japan, Yugoslavia 1932 (Reel 8, Side 1, Index 26), Reel 8, Side 1, Index 26 (Reel 8)
  - Country Files Special Projects - Austria, China 1936 (Reel 8, Side 2, Index 1), Reel 8, Side 2, Index 1 (Reel 8)
  - Country Files Special Projects - Czechoslovakia, Denmark 1936 (Reel 8, Side 2, Index 2), Reel 8, Side 2, Index 2 (Reel 8)
  - Country Files American University Union - France, Germany General, Latin America 1936-38 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 23), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 23 (Reel 7)
  - IIE Admin Board 1939-40 - England, France, Czech, League 1940 (Reel 9, Side 1, Index 18), Reel 9, Side 1, Index 18 (Reel 9)
  - Country Files Germany - Refugees Eric Franzen, Research League of Nations, Latin-America Coordinator's Office 1942 (Reel 12, Side 1, Index 10), Reel 12, Side 1, Index 10 (Reel 12)
  - Country Files American University Union - Britian, Foreign Colleges, China, Czechoslovakia, Department of State 1943 (Reel 12, Side 2, Index 38), Reel 12, Side 2, Index 38 (Reel 12)
  - Country Files Germanistic Society - India, Ireland, Latin America (1944) - Switzerland 1943 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 2), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 2 (Reel 13)
  - Country Folders Arabia, Austria, Canada, China, Czechoslovakia 1949 (Reel 17, Side 1, Index 23), Reel 17, Side 1, Index 23 (Reel 17)
  - Country Folders England, Finland, France, Germany 1949 (Reel 17, Side 1, Index 24), Reel 17, Side 1, Index 24 (Reel 17)
  - Country Folders Holland, Hungary, Iraq, Italy 1949 (Reel 17, Side 1, Index 25), Reel 17, Side 1, Index 25 (Reel 17)
  - Czechoslovakia - Czechoslovak - American Institute at Prague 1921-25 (Reel 2, Side 2, Index 6), Reel 2, Side 2, Index 6 (Reel 2)
  - Czechoslovakia General - Articles 1921-39 (Reel 9, Side 1, Index 8), Reel 9, Side 1, Index 8 (Reel 9)
  - Czechoslovakia 1928 See under Country Files 1928 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 2), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 2 (Reel 18)
  - Czechoslovakia 1933 (Reel 4, Side 1, Index 34), Reel 4, Side 1, Index 34 (Reel 4)
  - Czechoslovakia Washington and Ministry of Education 1933 (Reel 4, Side 1, Index 10), Reel 4, Side 1, Index 10 (Reel 4)
  - Czechoslovakia Washington and Ministry of Education 1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 16), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 16 (Reel 11)
  - Czechoslovakia Successful 1927-32, 1934 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 46), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 46 (Reel 10)
  - Czechoslovakia Dr. Professor J. Kose 1934 and 1937 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 15), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 15 (Reel 11)
  - Czechoslovakia 1935 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 41), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 41 (Reel 11)
  - Czechoslovakia Washington and Ministry of Education 1935 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 42), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 42 (Reel 11)
  - Czechoslovakia Successful 1931-32 and 1935 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 28), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 28 (Reel 10)
  - Czechoslovakia 1936 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 26), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 26 (Reel 7)
  - Czechoslovakia Washington and Ministry of Education 1936 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 27), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 27 (Reel 7)
  - Czechoslovakia - Czechoslovak Assisant 1936 (Reel 5, Side 2, Index 7), Reel 5, Side 2, Index 7 (Reel 5)
  - Special Projects Czechoslovakia Plan B 1937 (Reel 8, Side 2, Index 28), Reel 8, Side 2, Index 28 (Reel 8)
  - Czechoslovakia Washington and Ministry of Education 1939 (Reel 10, Side 1, Index 11), Reel 10, Side 1, Index 11 (Reel 10)
  - Czechoslovakia 1940 (Reel 10, Side 1, Index 30), Reel 10, Side 1, Index 30 (Reel 10)
  - Czechoslovakia Washington and Ministry of Education 1940 (Reel 10, Side 1, Index 15), Reel 10, Side 1, Index 15 (Reel 10)
  - Czechoslovakia Special Projects A-Z 1940 (Reel 21, Side 1, Index 26), Reel 21, Side 1, Index 26 (Reel 21)
  - Czechoslovakia Refugees 1940 (Reel 10, Side 1, Index 16), Reel 10, Side 1, Index 16 (Reel 10)
  - Czechoslovakia 1942 (Reel 12, Side 1, Index 33), Reel 12, Side 1, Index 33 (Reel 12)
  - Czechoslovakia Carnegie Endowment 1942 (Reel 12, Side 2, Index 1), Reel 12, Side 2, Index 1 (Reel 12)
  - Czechoslovakia 1943 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 7), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 7 (Reel 13)
  - Czechoslovakia 1944 (Reel 13, Side 2, Index 19), Reel 13, Side 2, Index 19 (Reel 13)
  - Czechoslovakia 1946 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 12), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 12 (Reel 15)
  - Czechoslovakia 1949 See under Country Folders 1949 (Reel 17, Side 1, Index 23), Reel 17, Side 1, Index 23 (Reel 17)
  - Czechoslovakia General - Student Exchange Lists - U.S. Students to Czechoslovakia - Summary of Applications 1949 (Reel 29, Side 1, Index 32), Reel 29, Side 1, Index 32 (Reel 29)
  - Czechoslovakia Dr. Matousek 1949 (Reel 17, Side 1, Index 17), Reel 17, Side 1, Index 17 (Reel 17)
  - Czechoslovakia Re Ministry of Education Fellowships for American Students - Leftist Activities 1949-50 (Reel 17, Side 1, Index 31), Reel 17, Side 1, Index 31 (Reel 17)
  - Department of State General 1943 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 8), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 8 (Reel 13)
  - Department of State 1943 See Under Country Files 1943 (Reel 12, Side 2, Index 38), Reel 12, Side 2, Index 38 (Reel 12)
  - IIE General Department of State Re Contract with IIE 1943-44 (Reel 18, Side 1, Index 21), Reel 18, Side 1, Index 21 (Reel 18)
  - General Department of State 1946 (Reel 14, Side 2, Index 11), Reel 14, Side 2, Index 11 (Reel 14)
  - General Department of State-IIE Re Student Exchange Contracts (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 34), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 34 (Reel 15)
  - General Department of State 1944 (Reel 13, Side 2, Index 6), Reel 13, Side 2, Index 6 (Reel 13)
  - Department of State Sargeant Report - International Exchange of Students and Industrial Trainees 1946 (Reel 23, Side 1, Index 3), Reel 23, Side 1, Index 3 (Reel 23)
  - IIE General Department of State-IIE Re Sergeant Report 1946-47 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 33), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 33 (Reel 15)
  - IIE General Department of State-IIE Problems of Liaison 1947 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 32), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 32 (Reel 15)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - Oxford University Debating Team - Anthony Wedgwood Benn - Davud K. Harris - Edward C. G. Boyle 1947-48 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 26), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 26 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - Oxford University Debating Team II - Anthony Wedgwood Benn 1947-48 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 27), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 27 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - Oxford University Debating Team III - Personal Correspondence - Finances and Reports 1947-48 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 28), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 28 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - General - Team Itineraries 1947-51 (Reel 25, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 25, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - General - Comments on Debaters 1948-51 (Reel 25, Side 2, Index 13), Reel 25, Side 2, Index 13 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - Cambridge Debating Team - Mr. Freeth and Mr. Pattison - Spring 1949, 1948-49 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 29), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 29 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - Cambridge Debating Team II - Mr. Cradock and Mr. Macrae - Spring 1949, 1948-49 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 30), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 30 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - Oxford University Debating Team - Mr. Robin Day and Mr. Geoffrey Johnson-Smith 1948-49 (Fall 1949) (Reel 25, Side 2, Index 1), Reel 25, Side 2, Index 1 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - Oxford University Debating Team II - Mr. Robin Day and Mr. Geoffrey Johnson-Smith (Fall 1949) (Reel 25, Side 2, Index 2), Reel 25, Side 2, Index 2 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - American Debating Team - Mr. Newton and Mr. Rabcliffe 1950 (Reel 25, Side 2, Index 3), Reel 25, Side 2, Index 3 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - American Debating Team - American Debaters in Britain - Re Comments 1950 (Reel 25, Side 2, Index 6), Reel 25, Side 2, Index 6 (Reel 25)
  - General - Britain American Debating Team - Opinions on English Tour 1950 (Reel 20, Side 2, Index 26), Reel 20, Side 2, Index 26 (Reel 20)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - Scottish Debating Team - Dr. Malcolm D.W. Low-Edinburgh, Mr. David D.T. Reis-Glasgow - Spring 1950 (Reel 25, Side 2, Index 7), Reel 25, Side 2, Index 7 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - Combined Universities Debating Team - E. Alwyn Smith and Gyynn Williams - Fall 1950 (Reel 25, Side 2, Index 4), Reel 25, Side 2, Index 4 (Reel 25)
  - Britain - Special Projects - General - Debating - Replies to Questionairre on History of International Debate 1950 (Reel 25, Side 2, Index 5), Reel 25, Side 2, Index 5 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - Japan - Debaters - Correspondence Re Japanese Debates 1950-55 (Reel 31, Side 1, Index 16), Reel 31, Side 1, Index 16 (Reel 31)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - General - Application Forms and Announcement 1951 (Reel 25, Side 2, Index 12), Reel 25, Side 2, Index 12 (Reel 25)
  - Britain - Special Projects - American Debating Team - Benjamin Crane and Joseph Barse - Spring 1951 (Reel 25, Side 2, Index 8), Reel 25, Side 2, Index 8 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - Cambridge Debating Team - Jack Ashley and Ronald Waterhouse - Spring 1951 (Reel 25, Side 2, Index 9), Reel 25, Side 2, Index 9 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - Oxford University Debating Team - William Rees-Mogg and Dick Taverne - Fall 1951 (Reel 25, Side 2, Index 10), Reel 25, Side 2, Index 10 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - Pakistan Debaters - American Debating Team - Mr. Harland Randolph and Mr. George Phillips - Correspondence, Proposals 1954 - 1951-54 (Reel 30, Side 2, Index 24), Reel 30, Side 2, Index 24 (Reel 30)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - Oxford University Debating Team II - William Rees-Mogg and Dick Taverne - Fall 1951 (Reel 25, Side 2, Index 11), Reel 25, Side 2, Index 11 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - Australian Debating Team - John Boyd Reid and Robin Millhouse - Spring 1952 - 1951-52 (Reel 25, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 25, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - Debaters - Australian Debating Team II - Robin R. Millhouse and John Boyd Reid - Spring 1952 (Reel 25, Side 2, Index 16), Reel 25, Side 2, Index 16 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projets - Debaters - American Debating Team to Australia and New Zealand - Henry Kiker - David Hunter - Summer 1952 (Reel 25, Side 2, Index 17), Reel 25, Side 2, Index 17 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - Combined Universities Debating Team - Kenneth F. Dibben and Ronald G. Evans - Fall 1952 (Reel 26, Side 1, Index 1), Reel 26, Side 1, Index 1 (Reel 26)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - Cambridge Debating Team - Alistair Sampson and Peter Mansfield - Spring 1953 (Reel 26, Side 1, Index 10), Reel 26, Side 1, Index 10 (Reel 26)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - Oxford University Debating Team - Patrick Mayhem and John Peters - Fall 1953 (Reel 26, Side 1, Index 7), Reel 26, Side 1, Index 7 (Reel 26)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - Oxford University Debating Team II - Patrick Mayhem and John Peters - Fall 1953 (Reel 26, Side 1, Index 8), Reel 26, Side 1, Index 8 (Reel 26)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - English-Speaking Union Re Oxford Debaters in Chicago - Fall 1953 (Reel 26, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 26, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 26)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - General Report on Debating in Great Britain (Richard King) Selection - Annual Leter 1953-54 (Reel 30, Side 2, Index 23), Reel 30, Side 2, Index 23 (Reel 30)
  - Special Projects - Britain Debaters - American Debating Teams Correspondence Re Seletion 1953-54 (Reel 30, Side 2, Index 35), Reel 30, Side 2, Index 35 (Reel 30)
  - Special Projects - Australia - Future Debaters 1954 (Reel 30, Side 2, Index 25), Reel 30, Side 2, Index 25 (Reel 30)
  - Special Projects - India Debaters I - Indian Debating Team - Mr. R.P. Sirkar and Mr. M.K. Chaturvedi - Spring 1954 (Reel 30, Side 2, Index 27), Reel 30, Side 2, Index 27 (Reel 30)
  - Special Projects - India Debaters II - Indian Debating Team - Mr. R.P. Sirkar and Mr. M.K. Chaturvedi - Spring 1954 (Reel 30, Side 2, Index 28), Reel 30, Side 2, Index 28 (Reel 30)